练习 2-10：T、D、S、Z 加 Y 的连读。请跟读下面内容。
Exercise 2-10, T, D, S, or Z, plus Y, liaisons. Repeat the following.
forgot. Is that your final answer? Natural, perpetual, virtual. Did you see
it? How'd you like it? Could you tell? Where'd you send your check? What'd your
family think? Did you find your keys? We followed your instructions.
Congratulations. Education. Individual. Graduation. Gradual. Yes you are.
Insurance. Bless you. Press your hands together. Can you dress yourself? You can
pass your exams this year I'll try to guess your age Let him guess your car for
you How is your family? How was your trip? Who's your friend? Where's your mom?
When's your birthday? She says you're okay Who does your hair? casual visual Usual.
Version. Vision.